("Single Ladies, Put A Ring On It")
♪ All the single ladies,
all the single ladies ♪
♪ All the single ladies ♪
♪ Now put your hands up ♪
♪ Up in the club, we just broke up ♪
♪ I'm doing my own little thing ♪
♪ Decided to dip and now you wanna trip ♪
♪ 'Cause another brother noticed me ♪
♪ I'm up on him, he up on me ♪
♪ Don't pay him any attention ♪
♪ Just cried my tears,
for three good years ♪
♪ Ya can't be mad at me ♪ ♪
'Cause if you liked it then ♪
♪ You should have put a ring on it ♪
♪ If you liked it then you
shoulda put a ring on it ♪
♪ Don't be mad once you
see that he want it ♪
♪ If you liked it then you
shoulda put a ring on it ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, o-oh ♪
♪ If you liked it then you
should have put a ring on it ♪
shoulda put a ring on it ♪
♪ Don't be mad once you
see that he want it ♪
♪ If you liked it then you
shoulda put a ring on it ♪
♪ I got gloss on my
lips, a man on my hips ♪
♪ Got me tighter in my Dereon jeans ♪
♪ Acting up, drink in my cup ♪
♪ I can care less what you think ♪
♪ I need no permission, did I mention ♪
♪ Don't pay him any attention ♪
♪ 'Cause you had your turn
and now you gonna learn ♪
♪ What it really feels like to miss me ♪
♪ 'Cause if you liked it then ♪
♪ You should have put a ring on it ♪
♪ If you liked it then you
shoulda put a ring on it ♪
♪ Don't be mad once you
see that he want it ♪
♪ If you liked it then you
shoulda put a ring on it ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ If you liked it then you
should have put a ring on it ♪
shoulda put a ring on it ♪
♪ Don't be mad once you
see that he want it ♪
♪ If you liked it then you
shoulda put a ring on it ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Don't treat me to the
things of the world ♪
♪ I'm not that kind of girl ♪
♪ Your love is what I
prefer, what I deserve ♪
♪ Here's a man that
makes me then takes me ♪
♪ And delivers me to a destiny,
to infinity and beyond ♪
♪ Pull me into your arms,
say I'm the one you own ♪
♪ If you don't, you'll be alone ♪
♪ And like a ghost I'll be gone ♪
♪ All the single ladies,
all the single ladies ♪
♪ All the single ladies ♪
♪ Now put your hands up,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ 'Cause if you liked it then ♪
♪ You should have put a ring on it ♪
♪ If you liked it then you
shoulda put a ring on it ♪
♪ Don't be mad once you
see that he want it ♪
♪ If you liked it then you
shoulda put a ring on it ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ If you liked it then you
should have put a ring on it ♪
shoulda put a ring on it ♪
♪ Don't be mad once you
see that he want it ♪
♪ If you liked it then you
shoulda put a ring on it ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
(light electronic buzzing)